Contact

nikhar.jain11@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nikhar444 (LinkedIn) nikhar444.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

C++

Java

Machine Learning

Certifications

Graphic Design Careers: First Steps PHP with MySQL Essential Training: 1 The Basics

AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate: 3 Virtual Private Cloud

AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate: 2 Storage Design

Learning Amazon Web Services (AWS) for Developers

Nikhar Jain

Machine Learning | Artificial Intelligence | MERN Stack | Google DSC Lead | SWE Intern ISRO'18

Jaipur Metro Rail Corporation

Summary

Experienced Coordinator with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in machine learning, Data Science, Java, HTML, Data Analysis, and Algorithms. Strong professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from Mody Institute of Technology & Science, Sikar.

Experience

Developer Student Clubs Lead August 2020 - Present (1 month)

Enginium

1 year 5 months

Head Designer
July 2020 - Present (2 months)

Coordinator

April 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Sikar Area, India

Cats Winter of Code Core Developer June 2020 - Present (3 months)

Text Mercato Solutions Private Limited Machine Learning Intern May 2020 - August 2020 (4 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka

The Foundation for Youth Social Entrepreneurship (FYSE) Project Coordinator September 2019 - August 2020 (1 year) DoITC : Department of Information Technology & Communication, Government of Rajasthan(India) Full Stack Engineer May 2020 - July 2020 (3 months)

GirlScript Summer of Code Open Source Contributor February 2020 - June 2020 (5 months)

EasyA

Full Stack Engineer April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)

Entrepreneurship Development Cell Program Coordinator July 2019 - May 2020 (11 months)

Udacity

Intel® Edge Al Tech scholar
December 2019 - March 2020 (4 months)

Society of Women Engineers Member January 2019 - February 2020 (1 year 2 months) Sikar Area, India

Corum8

Business Development Specialist August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months)

IEEE

Program Coordinator July 2019 - January 2020 (7 months) Jaipur Area, India

Mozilla

Member September 2017 - September 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Scanta

Machine Learning Intern May 2019 - July 2019 (3 months)

Gurgaon, Haryana, India

Working on a product based on Emotional Intelligence

Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay Trainee November 2018 - January 2019 (3 months)

ISRO - Indian Space Research Organization Intern May 2018 - July 2018 (3 months) Jodhpur, Rajasthan, India

Worked on MongoDB

AutoKartz
Freelance Technical Writer
February 2018 - May 2018 (4 months)
Noida Area, India

EduMorf India Private Limited Technical Writer September 2017 - November 2017 (3 months)

Education

Mody Institute of Technology & Science, Sikar Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

delhi public school jodhpur PCM · (2010 - 2017)

Rajmata Krishna Kumari Girls' Public School (2006 - 2009)